RG 071:003, Department of Housing Planning Maps
Connecticut State Library
Department of Housing planning maps
circa 1943-1980
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. Dept. of Housing
8 cubic feet
Town planning maps created through HUD's 701 Planning and Management Assistance Program.
RG071_003
T003133
Historical Note
The U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD) operated a Comprehensive Planning Assistance Grant program, also known as the 701 Planning and Management Assistance Program. Grants were awarded at the state, regional, and local level to improve housing and land use planning and management.
Scope and Content
Maps of various types including zoning, base, land use, population density, traffic flow and volumes, utilities, neighborhoods, topopgraphy, community facilities, and buildable land, among others.
Arrangement
Alphabetical by town. Maps within towns are in no partcular order.
Related Material
None.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. Dept. of Community Affairs; Connecticut. Dept. of Housing
Subjects:
City planning -- Connecticut -- maps; Connecticut. Dept. of Housing -- Records and correspondence; Connecticut. Dept. of Community Affairs -- Records and correspondence; Federal aid to community development; Zoning -- Connecticut -- maps
Document Types:
Maps
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Dept. of Community Affairs. Planning Maps, circa 1943-1980
  - Andover (Box 1)
    - Zoning map, 1959 August 13; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      701 project: Conn. P-12
      plan number: IV-A-2
    - Base map, 1959 August 13; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: I-B
    - Land use, 1959 August 13; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.5 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 1)
      plan number: II-A
    - General zoning, 1959 August 13; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.5 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 1)
      plan number: II-E
    - Public utilities, 1959 August 13; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: III-F
    - Area of influence base map, 1959 October 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.5 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 1)
      plan number: I-A
    - Base map for center, 1959 October 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.5 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: I-D
    - Area of influence traffic patterns, 1959 October 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.5 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 1)
      plan number: II-B
    - Area of influence major watersheds, 1959 October 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.5 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 1)
      plan number: II-C
    - Road conditions, 1959 October 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.75 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: III-D
    - Andover lake district, 1959 October 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: I-E
    - Slope map, 1959 October 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.75 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: III-G
    - Land types, 1959 October 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.75 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: III-H
    - Water courses and water holes, 1959 November 13; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.75 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: III-E
    - Existing and projected traffic volumes, 1959 November 20; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: IV-B
    - Existing population density, 1960 June 6; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.75 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: III-B-1
    - Community facilities, 1960 July 7; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.75 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: IV-D
    - Study for new center, 1960 July 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.75 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: V-A,B
    - Recommendations Andover lake district, 1960 July 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: V-D
    - Area of influence population and density, 1960 July 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.75 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 1)
      plan number: II-D
    - Town budget, 1960 July 31; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.5 in. (Box 1)
      plan number: III-J
    - Suggested capital improvement projects, undated; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 36.25 x 29.75 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: IV-C
  - Ansonia (Box 1)
    - Legend only, undated; approximately 14.5 x 42.5 in. (Box 1)
    - Central business district, 1956 May; George M. Raymond Associates; 39.75 x 36.25 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 1)
      701 project: Conn. P-1
    - Proposed zoning, 1956 May; George M. Raymond Associates; 47.5 x 41.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 1)
    - Land use, 1956 May; George M. Raymond Associates; 47.5 x 41.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 1)
    - Base map, 1956 May; George M. Raymond Associates; 47.5 x 41.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 1)
    - Map 1, Circulation plan, 1965 June; Brent B. Friedlander; 51 x 41.25 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 1)
      701 project: Conn. P-48
    - Map 2, Recreation plan, 1965 June; Brent B. Friedlander; 51 x 41.75 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 1)
    - Map 3, Alternate central business plans, 1965 June; 42.5 x 28 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 1)
  - Avon (Box 1)
    - Town center, 1954 June; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner; 37.5 x 26.25 in.; 1 inch = 500 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: 6-53
    - Highway classification and basic design standards, 1955 September; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32.25 x 20.75 in. (Box 1)
      plan number: 7-01
    - Subdivisions street cross-sections drainage facilities, 1955 September; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32.25 x 20.75 in. (Box 1)
      plan number: 7-02
    - Subdivisions street design, 1955 September; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32.25 x 20.75 in. (Box 1)
      plan number: 7-03
    - Subdivisions model layout, 1955 September; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32.25 x 20.75 in. (Box 1)
      plan number: 7-04
    - Subdivision requirements and floor area relations for new business units, 1955 September; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 32.25 x 20.75 in. (Box 1)
      plan number: 7-05
    - Circulation plan, 1956 June 5; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 39.25 x 26.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: 6-64
    - Circulation plan, 1956 June 6; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 39.25 x 26.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: 6-65
    - Buildability plan, 1956 June 11; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 39 x 26.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: 6-60
    - Buildability plan, 1956 June 12; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 38.5 x 26.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: 6-61
    - Town utilities plan, 1956 June 15; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 39 x 26.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: 6-66
    - Town utilities plan, 1956 June 16; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 38.5 x 26.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: 6-67
    - Subdivision map, 1956 June 18; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 38.5 x 26.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: 6-71
    - Subdivision map, 1956 June 18; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 39 x 26.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: 6-70
    - Future land use, 1956 June 18; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 39 x 26.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: 6-58
    - Future land use, 1956 June 19; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 39 x 26.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: 6-59
    - Residential density, 1956 June 21; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 39.25 x 26.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: 6-62
    - Residential density, 1956 June 23; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 38.5 x 26.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: 6-63
    - Flood-prone land, 1957 February 26; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 38.5 x 26.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: 3-15
    - Flood-prone land, 1957 February 26; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 39 x 26.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
    - Flood damage to dwellings, business, industry and public utilities, 1957 April 11; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 39 x 26.25 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: 3-16
    - Flood damage to dwellings, business, industry and public utilities, 1957 April 11; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 38.5 x 26 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
    - North east part Talcott Mountain, 1957 May 29; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 38 x 29.75 in.; 1 inch = 500 feet (Box 1)
    - South part of center base map, 1957 May 29; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 38 x 29.75 in.; 1 inch = 500 feet (Box 1)
    - South east part of Talcott Mountain, 1957 May 29; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 38 x 29.75 in.; 1 inch = 500 feet (Box 1)
    - Regional 1st and 2nd ring towns; regional with streams and major streets, 1957 May 29; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 37.5 x 26.25 in.; 1 inch = 2 miles (Box 1)
      plan number: I-A, I-B
    - Town and abutting areas, 1957 May 29; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 37.25 x 26 in.; 1 inch = .5 mile (Box 1)
      plan number: I-C
    - Base map - no central part of town, 1957 May 29; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 38 x 29.75 in.; 1 inch = 500 feet (Box 1)
    - Zoning map, 1969 August 12; Town of Avon engineering department and Technical Planning Associates; 22.5 x 17.5 in. (Box 1)
    - Public improvement program A, undated; M. H. Lincoln; 28.5 x 21 in. (Box 1)
    - Public improvement program B, undated; Technical Planning Associates Inc.; 28.5 x 21.5 in. (Box 1)
    - Base map entire town, undated; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 39.5 x 28.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
    - Tunxis reservation, undated; Dr. Joseph R. Moschner and Associates; 45.5 x 32.5 in. (Box 1)
      plan number: I-M
  - Beacon Falls (Box 1)
    - Regional circulation, 1956 May; F. C. Clark and Associates; 27.25 x 22.75 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 1)
    - Base map no legend, 1956 May; F. C. Clark and Associates; 27..25 x 22.5 in.; 1 inch = .5 mile (Box 1)
    - Drainage basins, 1956 July; 28.625 x 22.625 in.; 1 inch = .5 mile (Box 1)
    - Redevelopment map, 1956 August; Gates and Ford and Shapiro Associates; 25 x 15 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 1)
    - Land slope, 1956 August 14; 27.625 x 22.75 in.; 1 inch = 31680 feet (Box 1)
    - Land slope, 1956 August 14; 28.25 x 22.625 in.; 1 inch = .5 mile (Box 1)
    - Plan of development, 1956 August; Gates and Ford and Shapiro Associates; 33.25 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Recent housing, 1956 August; Gates and Ford and Shapiro Associates; 37 x 27.625 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Utilities plan, 1956 August; Gates and Ford and Shapiro Associates; 36.5 x 27.25 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Circulation plan, 1956 August; Gates and Ford and Shapiro Associates; 35.625 x 27 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Industrial and central business district plan, 1956 August; Gates and Ford and Shapiro Associates; 35.5 x 26.75 in.; 1 inch = 500 feet (Box 1)
    - Circulation deficiencies, 1956 August; Gates and Ford and Shapiro Associates; 36.5 x 27 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - 1955 traffic volumes, 1956 August; Gates and Ford and Shapiro Associates; 36.5 x 28 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Population, 1956 August; Gates and Ford and Shapiro Associates; 35.5 x 26.125 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Existing utilities, 1956 August; Gates and Ford and Shapiro Associates; 34.75 x 26.25 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Neighborhood map, 1956 August; Gates and Ford and Shapiro Associates; 37 x 27.875 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Land use, 1956 August; Gates and Ford and Shapiro Associates; 33.75 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Neighborhood areas plan, 1956 August; Gates and Ford and Shapiro Associates; 36.5 x 27.75 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Existing land use central area, 1956 August; Gates and Ford and Shapiro Associates; 35.75 x 27 in.; 1 inch = 500 feet (Box 1)
    - Proposed residential densities, 1956 August; Gates and Ford and Shapiro Associates; 37.25 x 28.25 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Watershed, 1956 August; Gates and Ford and Shapiro Associates; 33.5 x 25 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Flood and steep slopes, 1956 August; Gates and Ford and Shapiro Associates; 33.375 x 24.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Topographic base map, 1956 August; Gates and Ford and Shapiro Associates; 33.5 x 24.75 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Land use, 1956 December; 28.5 x 22.75 in.; 1 inch = .5 mile (Box 1)
  - Berlin (Box 1)
    - Base map, 1956 December; Edward L. Davis Jr.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
      701 project: Conn. P-5
      In two parts. Part 1: 21.5 x 48.5 in.; part 2: 28 x 50.5 in.
    - Traffic and transportation survey, 1956 December; Fredrick P. Clark and Associates; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
      In two parts. Part 1: 21.5 x 48 in.; part 2: 28 x 50.5 in.
    - Proposed land use plan (Berlin Turnpike), 1957 October 8; Fredrick P. Clark and Associates; 34.5 x 58.5 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 1)
    - Public facilities plan, 1958 December; Fredrick P. Clark and Associates; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
      701 project: Conn. P-10
      In two parts. Top half: 24 x 50 in.; bottom half: 28.5 x 50 in.
    - Generalized land use plan, 1957 November 19; Fredrick P. Clark and Associates; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
      In two parts. Top half: 22.75 x 50 in.; bottom half: 29.5 x 50 in.
    - Topography, 1956 December; Fredrick P. Clark and Associates; 63.5 x 51.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Storm drainage, 1958 December 1; Edward L. Davis Jr.; 47 x 50.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Major drainage areas, 1957 January 10; Fredrick P. Clark and Associates; 63.5 x 51.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Zoning map, 1962 September; S. Spielvogel & Associates; 36.75 x 60 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
      701 project: Conn. P-29
    - Distribution of dwelling units, 1956 December; Fredrick P. Clark and Associates; 49.5 x 49.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - School and recreation plan, 1958 December; Fredrick P. Clark and Associates; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
      In two parts. Top half: 24 x 50 in.; bottom half: 28.25 x 50 in.
    - Water and sanitary sewer plan, 1958 December 1; Edward L. Davis Jr.; 47 x 50.25 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Community facilities, 1957 September; Fredrick P. Clark and Associates; 50.25 x 49.75 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Utilities, 1957 May 1; Fredrick P. Clark and Associates; 51 x 49.75 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Base map, 1956 December; Edward L. Davis Jr.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 1)
      In four parts. Part 1: 37.5 x 48.5 in.; part 2: 37 x 48.25 in.; part 3: 37.25 x 48.5 in.; part 4: 37 x 48.5 in.
    - Street and highway plan, 1958 December; Fredrick P. Clark and Associates; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
      In two parts. Top half: 23.75 x 50 in.; bottom half: 28.5 x 50 in.
  - Bethany (Box 1)
    - Area of influence base map, undated; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.25 x 34 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 1)
      701 project: Conn. P-21
    - Town base map, undated; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 34 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
    - Topography, undated; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 33.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
    - Town center base map, undated; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 33.75 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 1)
    - Area of influence generalized land use, 1961 June 16; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.25 x 34.125 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 1)
    - Area of influence traffic volumes, 1961 June 16; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 34 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 1)
    - Area of influence regional drainage, 1961 June 16; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 33.75 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 1)
    - Area of influence population growth and density, 1961 June 16; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.25 x 33.75 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 1)
    - Area of influence existing regional zoning, 1961 June 16; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 34 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 1)
    - Area of influence existing land use, 1961 June 16; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 34 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: III-A
    - Residential population density, 1961 June 16; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.25 x 34 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: III-B
    - Population trends, 1961 June 16; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.25 x 34 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: III-C
    - Road conditions, 1961 June 16; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.25 x 33.75 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
    - Water resources, 1961 June 16; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.25 x 33.75 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
    - Utilities, 1961 June 16; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 34 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
    - Buildable land, 1961 June 16; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.25 x 33.75 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
    - Existing zoning, 1958 June 19; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 34 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
    - Proposed land use, undated; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 34 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: IV-A
    - Traffic volumes, 1961 June 16; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 34 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
    - Capital improvements, undated; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 34 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
    - Community facilities, undated; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 34 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
    - Proposed land use, undated; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 34 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: IV-A-X
    - Town center illustrative site plan, 1962 March 27; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 34 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: V
    - Tentative zoning, undated; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 34 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: VI-A-2
    - Tentative zoning, undated; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42.5 x 34 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: VI-A-2-X
  - Bethel (Box 1)
    - Existing land use, 1957; Gates and Ford; 47.5 x 34.125 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
      701 project: Conn. P-8
      plan number: A-2
    - Present Utilities central area, 1957; Gates and Ford; 49.125 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 300 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: A-3
    - Present utilities, 1957; Gates and Ford; 47.625 x 33.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Existing conditions: schools, 1957; Gates and Ford; 47.5 x 33.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: A-4
    - Analysis of residential growth, 1957; Gates and Ford; 47.5 x 33.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: A-5
    - Transportation study part 1, 1957; Gates and Ford; 48.25 x 34.375 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: A-6
    - Transportation study part 2, 1957; Gates and Ford; 47.375 x 34 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
    - Analysis of land attractive to development, 1957; Gates and Ford; 48.75 x 34 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: B-2
    - Proposed facilities, 1957; Gates and Ford; 51 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: C-4
    - Proposed utilities, 1957; Gates and Ford; 52.125 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: C-5
    - Comprehensive plan of development, 1957; Gates and Ford; 48.25 x 34.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: C-6
    - Proposed zoning map, 1957; Gates and Ford; 48 x 33.75 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: D-1
    - Base map, 1957; Gates and Ford; 50.75 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: A-1-a
    - Central base map, 1957; Gates and Ford; 48.25 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 300 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: A-1-b
    - Topography base map, 1957; Gates and Ford; 51 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: A-1-c
    - Topography central base map, 1957; Gates and Ford; 45.75 x 35.5 in.; 1 inch = 300 feet (Box 1)
      plan number: A-1-d
    - Area of influence base map, 1953; Gates and Ford; 36.75 x 30.25 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 1)
      plan number: A-1-e
    - Proposed population densities, undated; 17.5 x 13.5 in.; 1 inch = .5 mile (Box 1)
    - Proposed population densities, undated; Gates and Ford; 11 x 8.5 in. (Box 1)
  - Bloomfield (Box 2)
    - Zoning map, 1962 March 27; 20.5 x 26 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 2)
    - Neighborhood analysis deterioration by neighborhood, 1967; Brown, Donald and Donald; 57.5 x 54.25 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 2)
      701 project: Conn. P-69
    - Neighborhood analysis base map, 1967; Brown, Donald and Donald; 53 x 42.25 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 2)
    - Neighborhood analysis non-residential deterioration, 1967; Brown, Donald and Donald; 53.25 x 42.25 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 2)
    - Neighborhood analysis land use, 1967; Brown, Donald and Donald; 59 x 42.25 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 2)
    - Neighborhood analysis neighborhood study areas, 1967; Brown, Donald and Donald; 55.75 x 42.375 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 2)
    - Neighborhood analysis base map, 1967; Brown, Donald and Donald; 53 x 42.25 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 2)
    - Neighborhood analysis proposed neighborhood plan for blue hills, 1967; Brown, Donald and Donald; 22 x 20 in. (Box 2)
    - Neighborhood analysis dwelling unit locations, 1967 April; Brown, Donald and Donald; 53.625 x 42.25 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 2)
    - Neighborhood analysis municipal facilities, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 53.75 x 42.25 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 2)
  - Bozrah (Box 2)
    - Land use, 1980; 42 x 34 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
  - Bridgeport (Box 2)
    - Existing land use, 1974 June; 32 x 24 in.; 1.375 inch = 1 mile (Box 2)
    - Existing zoning, 1974 June; 33 x 24 in.; 1.375 inch = 1 mile (Box 2)
  - Bristol (Box 2)
    - Building zone map, 1974 January; Division of Engineering; 21 x 21 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 1
    - Building zone map, 1974 January; Division of Engineering; 21 x 21 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 2
    - Building zone map, 1974 January; Division of Engineering; 21 x 21 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 3
    - Building zone map, 1974 January; Division of Engineering; 21 x 21 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 4
    - Existing land use, Technical Planning Associates, Inc.; 31.5 x 27 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 2)
  - Brooklyn (Box 2)
    - Base map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51.75 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 1-a
    - Base map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51.25 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 1-b
    - Base map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 1-c
    - Plan of development, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 50 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 2-a
    - Plan of development, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
    - Existing street classification, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 50.625 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 3-a
    - Existing street classification, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51.5 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 3-b
    - Traffic accident locations-1968-1967, Brown, Donald and Donald; 51.25 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 4-a
    - Traffic accident locations-1968-1968, Brown, Donald and Donald; 51.625 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 4-b
    - Slope map, 1968; Brown, Donald and Donald; 51.25 x 36.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 2)
      plan number: 5-a